ALL CHARACTERS, INCIDENTS, ORGANIZATIONS,
AND BACKGROUND ARE FICTITIOUS
EPISODE 1
100 PERCENT PURE CARBONIC ACID
THIS IS THE TASTE OF TRUE BEER
Yes. The story will be published shortly,
at around 7 a.m.
But I said to Despatch, "Interlocking
fingers doesn't mean they're dating.
Ask anyone you see on the streets."
And if you look closely,
they aren't interlocked.
You're holding his wrist.
So I said, "They're obviously not dating."
I strongly denied it,
and we concluded that you two
are good friends who like to pull pranks.
You call that a prank?
Yes. I told them you two are very close
and that's how you usually fool around...
I mean, that's how
you two usually hang out.
THOSE TWO ARE DEFINITELY DATING
Right.
We were close.
Although it's all over now.
PLEASE LET ME JUST GO HOME
All right.
It already happened, so it's fine.
It's all good,
but can you do something
about the blur effect?
Should I tell them to blur your face more?
No, that's not what I'm saying.
They blurred my earrings too.
It's the accessory item I'm promoting
the hardest out of the whole collection.
The blur effect should be...
How shall I put this?
Can they carefully shrink it
so that the earrings show right away?
Actually, a full shot would be better.
That way, people can see my purse
-and shoes too.
-Got it.
Purchasing Manager.
What should you do, then?
-Pardon me?
-The earrings, purse, and shoes.
You need to secure enough stock.
Orders will pile up
when they start trending.